





Kapil Prasad Prusty Kapil Prasad Prusty premium Featured PMP, SCJP, CSPO Sr. Engineering Manager seeking roles in Application Development, Program Management, Project Management, Production Support, Waterfall, Agile, Scrum, Java, J2EE, Spring, Hibernate, Struts, iBatis, EJB, JSP, Servlet, iText, Apache POI, REST Webservices Current Designation: Senior Engineering Manager - Java/J2EE Total Experience: 20 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Company: Dell Notice Period: 2 Months Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Metallurgy] Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming Maintenance Role: Program Mar Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Married Key Skills: Sr. Engineering Manager, Program Manager, Application Development, Program Management, Project Management.Production Support, Waterfall, Agile, Scrum, Java, J2EE, Spring, Hibernate, Struts, iBatis, EJB, JSP, SerVet, iText, Apache POI, REST Webservices,jUnit,Ant,Maven Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: Jan-Mar 2021 Last Modified: Jan-Mar 2021

Jump to Section | Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

20 years of IT experience in application development, testing and production support 9+ years of experience in people management & program / project management Working in DELL International Services Ltd since Jan 2019 as Senior Engineering Manager Managing a team of 30+ people, delivering project(s) worth 1M\$ to 2M\$ year on year Trained and Certified in Waterfall and Agile, Scrum, XP, Kanban, LeSS, SAFe & DevOps Experience in leading global programs, and executing projects in parallel 12 years of hands on experience in Java / J2EE, Spring, Hibernate, Struts, iBatis, EJB, JSP / Servlet, iText, Apache POI, REST Webservices, jUnit, Ant, Maven, WebLogic, Tomcat, Jenkins, Oracle DB, SAP Ariba etc Experience in HP Agile Manager, HP ALM, HP UFT, HP LoadRunner, HP Service Manager Experience in executing projects in different technology stacks

Work Experience

- De II as Senior Engineering Manager -Java/J2EE Jan 2019 to Till Date
- Dell Technologies as Senior Engineering Manager -Java/J2EE Jan 2019 to Jan 2019

LKB - Dell & EMC Articles Authoring Tool Integration - Jan 2020 till date Order Support Redesign and Customer Onboarding - Jan 2020 to Jul 2020 PCF (Pivotal Cloud) Mgration (FlatContent & Manuals) - Dec 2019 to Apr 2020 Dell & EMC Support website Integration - April 2019 to Nov 2019

• Hewlett Packard Enterprise (DXC Technology) as Delivery Manager Jul 2003 to Dec 2018

Action Lifecycle Management (Multiple Projects) - Mar 2012 to Dec 2020 DXC SMO Program (Perspecta) - Jan 2019 to July 2019 HPE DMO Program - Nov 2014 to Oct 2015 HP SMO Program - Nov 2014 to Oct 2015 ESIT Cloud Mgration (50+ applications) - Mar 2013 to Nov 2013

Satyam Computer Services Pvt Ltd as Systems Analyst (Project Lead) Nov 2000 to Jul 2003

Product Catalog - Client: DST Interactive - War 2001 to July 2003

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Metallurgy) from REC (NIT) Rourkela in 1997

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Java / J2EE			
Spring			
Hibernate			
Struts, iBatis, EJB, JSP			
SERVLET			
iText, Apache POI			
REST Webservices			
Ant, Maven, WebLogic			
Tomcat, Jenkins, Oracle DB			
SAP Ariba			
HP Agile Manager			
HP ALM, HP UFT			
HP LOADRUNNER			
HP Service Manager			
SAP Business Objects			
QlikView, Salesforce			
SQL Server DB			
Mongo DB, jQuery			
NodeJS, AngularJS			
.NET & Hadoop			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.